let's learn a little about each other
right up front how many of you like me
think it's bizarre to think that one day
there's gonna be grandmothers named
Brittany my grandma amber my grandma
Kaitlin that's gonna be a real thing in
35 years she'll be married to Grandpa
Hudson it's weird right
and I hope they name their kids Edith
and Mabel and we come full circle I hope
that
so you gotta I did something that people
never do anymore and I didn't realize it
till I did it I gave my children first
names
that's um II don't feel bad it's a trend
on of you some of you're sitting right
here with last names his first names you
know what I'm talking about
Taylor Tyler Tucker Tanner Mason Morgan
Madison Connor Carson Jackson Jefferson
Hunter Logan Flynn these are last names
and if you have two last names you sound
like a walking law firm that's what you
sound like
and that's too much pressure to go to
college kid named hunter Flynn can't dig
ditches he's got to make something out
of himself right what'd I say people do
this I meet Americans this is strictly
an American problem you've never met a
Mexican guy who said hi I'm Lopez Gomez
you've never met never was
hasn't really taken off in that culture
if you know anything now to be careful
what to name children even if you think
you've been careful you got to watch out
for initials especially like if you got
a last name with a double meaning like I
do I was at my mother's house helping
her clean out old boxes we found a
flight itinerary back in the days before
the internet had everything they used to
mail you an itinerary for everybody who
was going on the trip had all your last
names we all have the same last name of
my family and the first initial of
everybody else our last name is straight
my name is Christopher my brother's name
is Patrick see straight and P straight
[Music]
I'm 43 my brother is 36 it never dawned
on this woman until that moment what she
had done she sees that and just starts
laughing hysterically I stopped right
what are you laughing at you named us
she goes no that's not why it's funny I
got well then why is it funny because
you're blind as a bat and your brother
can't aim you really are in that Joe
come on he really did rough haven't kid
I got kids myself four kids and they
were my daughter's my oldest I remember
I'm realizing when she was born people
who try to help out parents now in ways
they didn't used to before like there
was the free meal for a while they
remember that every restaurant you went
to kids eat free kids eat free don't
they always
were you splitting the check with a
six-year-old before that time was the
kid offering I want to meet this kid he
stands up when the check gets there no
mom dad I got this I got this
you guys work hard and I just sold the
tree house got a big Commission so
obviously these restaurants their heart
is in the right place but I think it
would be more fair if they gave a
discount for the whole table based on
the amount of kids you had but no it's
exactly what it sounds like kids eat
free adults full price so they make you
lie to them oh the kids eat free but we
got to pay then I'll have the jello and
he'll have the steak yeah 20 ounce
t-bone put it on the high chair you
heard me that's it we're gonna be a
while he kind of gums it to death is
that okay with you